[Neferpitou] Oh, yeah, it's so simple.
All I need to do is fix him.
That's what I'm gonna make my ability.
The only question is
how we'll manage to win.
If you have any ideas,
I'd be glad to hear them.
You love to tease, don't you?
At this rate, you're never going to
defeat Knuckle and Shoot,
much less the Chimera Ants.
[Gon] No way.
We'll never give up.
We will go back to the NGL.
I don't care what we have to do.
[singer singing in Japanese]
[singer singing in English]
DUEL X AND X ESCAPE
[narrator] As the Queen
prepares for labor,
she requires the equivalent
of 250 human meatballs per day
in order to give birth to a strong king.
[heart beating]
[gasps]
[heart continues beating]
[grunting]
[grunting continues]
[Palm] I have to wonder.
Will this be enough?
Can they execute the plan
to slaughter Morel's pupils?
[Biscuit] Okay, all done!
[boys groan]
You two finally held out
for three whole hours.
-[both panting]
-We did it. That was hard.
No kidding. I can't even move an inch.
Don't be silly. Get back up.
Going where?
-To see Knuckle, of course.
-[both gasp]
[Killua] But why?
See? You can move after all. Let's go.
But why are we gonna go see Knuckle?
[groans] Don't ask
when the answer is obvious.
To fight him!
[both gasp]
[gasps]
[Biscuit] Now let's go!
What the hell are you talking about?
We still have some time, don't we?
What matters now is who gets the tiles.
-You got it?
-[Gon] Yeah.
That means
you'll have to take theirs at any cost.
If it looks like you're going to lose,
run away, and try again the next day.
So, three hours of Ren practice a day.
After that, you'll challenge Knuckle
and keep at it until you win.
[Knuckle groans]
No one today either.
Hmm. Now, who's your owner?
-Oh, they're bad owners, aren't they?
-[whines]
[chuckles] Stop it. That tickles.
Hey, knock it off.
I said stop, okay? [laughs]
Uh… [clears throat]
-Do you think that's Knuckle?
-I do.
[gasps]
I can't believe this.
It's you two? Really?
[both grunt]
[gasps]
[growls]
Well, well, well.
I guess they don't have
much respect for me.
[both gasp]
[Knuckle] If I'm being compared
to a couple of snot-nosed little kids,
[growls]
[Gon] What a presence.
[Killua straining] We should act first,
but we can't move.
[both gasp]
There's no way you punks can defeat me.
I'm not upset at all.
These are just… They're, uh…
They're tears from laughing too much,
you fool.
Don't tell anyone about this,
or I'll murder you.
[both] Huh?
I'll show you just how much stronger I am,
and once I do, you'll see that
I don't even need to dodge your punches.
Hit me to your heart's content.
But if I don't budge an inch… And I won't…
You have to leave your tiles behind
and walk away.
That's the best deal you'll ever get!
You're both insane if you think
you can pick a fight with me at your age.
[Killua] Well, you're the one
who challenged us to a duel.
Is what I want to say.
But I can tell.
We're nowhere near Knuckle's level,
[Gon] Fact is we can't overcome everything
with willpower.
I don't have any comebacks,
but I'm not just gonna
stand here and take it.
Just so you know, I won't stop hitting you
until you move, all right?
Less talk, more action.
Do what you gotta do.
[Gon grunts] Show me rock!
[gasps]
[Knuckle] Whoa, whoa, whoa.
I'll use Gyo.
Wait! I have to defend with Ko.
Crap!
But where do I defend?
Think.
I'd expect him to attack the belly.
That's his only real choice.
That must be it, the belly.
[Gon] Jan…
[Knuckle] Yes, it's the belly!
Belly, belly, belly!
[Gon] …ken…
-[rumbling]
-[glass cracking]
[body thudding]
[dog whimpers]
[gasps]
Uh…
And you didn't…
let me down. Thanks.
[groans]
What's with this guy? Is he crazy?
Hey! Look who's awake.
[groans]
You're stronger than I realized.
I'll give you credit.
Guess I really should have before.
[Killua chuckles softly]
ROOK
[Knuckle] Why didn't you take this?
That tile, it isn't what we were after.
All we wanted was to be able to beat you
in a battle fair and square.
Can I ask you something?
Uh, sure. So what is it you wanna know?
Why did you wanna become a Beast Hunter?
[Knuckle] Hmm? [sighs]
It's a pretty long story,
one that brings back
a whole bunch of bad memories.
In that case, why did you volunteer
for the Extermination Team?
My master says I'm naive,
but I don't care.
If you've never seen something,
then you don't have the right
to pass judgment on it.
[Killua] Only problem is
you'll get yourself killed that way.
[Gon chuckles softly]
You're a real good kid.
I knew the moment
we started duking it out.
-You, too, Mr. Knuckle.
-Eh?
[Gon grunts]
Uh…
[whining]
[Knuckle] It's you!
[Gon] Yeah.
We couldn't get him to leave your side.
-[whimpering, barking]
-I've heard it said
that good Hunters
are well liked by animals.
[whimpering]
I'm so close to Morel's pupil.
[chomping]
Wow, this is delicious!
[gasps]
Fight me whenever you want.
[boys] Huh?
[Knuckle] You can take
all the tries you need.
But we only have 20 days left now,
so it's not like you can beat me.
[both chuckle softly]
[Knuckle sighs] So good.
What's all this smoke?
Where is it coming from?
[yells]
[gasping]
Where am I?
Let's get this started, shall we?
[Colt] What?
Chiona's squadron is missing?
That's right.
And was it the same way
that Reikei's disappeared?
Yes, it appears so.
The leader went missing first,
then the rest of them vanished one by one.
Hmm.
and the food is scattering farther away.
If humans target us in a long hunt,
it could mean trouble for us, and a lot.
[sighs] Though that idea
doesn't thrill me at all.
[machinery humming]
[liquid bubbling]
Mmm. Needs to be
more concentrated, I think.
[Peggy] Just as expected.
Well, this is better
than getting erratic orders, I suppose.
We should begin by determining
our current troop strength.
How many squadron leaders?
[Peggy] Assuming Chiona was taken out,
28 remain.
[Colt] Each squadron leader
has four officers
and, in some cases, five,
And the four squadrons that are missing
fall under the latter category?
I highly doubt
that they would listen to advice.
[Netero] If you ask me,
I'd say that's the strategy
they've come up with by now.
Well, we should be able
to keep the current plan then.
Actually, I think it might be good
to tangle with a trap
every once in a while.
If all goes well, we'll eliminate
another three or four squads
we'll finish up
before reinforcements arrive.
I hope…
[wind blowing]
…things go that way.
[both panting]
[Knuckle] Here.
-[dogs whining]
-Huh?
There are more of you guys
than I realized.
-Well, don't hold back. Go on and eat too.
-[dog barks]
[Knuckle chuckles]
[chuckles]
[grunts]
They came back.
I can take on both of you at once.
You think you're better than us,
but I don't give a damn.
We're still more than happy to accept.
[grunting]
[Gon grunts]
[screams]
Give me a break.
I could keep playing with you kids,
but I just don't have that kind of time.
[yelling]
Now that's more like it. Ha!
Their bodies are worn out.
All that's moving them now
is sheer willpower.
Once they've accomplished
the task at hand,
their renewed confidence
will allow them to improve exponentially.
That ain't gonna happen!
[closing theme music playing]
[singer singing in Japanese]
[Gon] Next time,
Rock-Paper-Scissors and Weakness.
Killua! Tickle, tickle, tickle!
[Killua laughs] Stop. It's my turn.
[singer singing in Japanese]